<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-10-23T14:05:02+05:30</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">jesly.varghese</title><subtitle>Personal webspace of Jesly Varghese.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">101 Days Of Image Processing</title><link href="/image-processing/image/computer-science/2017/10/23/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="101 Days Of Image Processing" /><published>2017-10-23T13:56:19+05:30</published><updated>2017-10-23T13:56:19+05:30</updated><id>/image-processing/image/computer-science/2017/10/23/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="/image-processing/image/computer-science/2017/10/23/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;101-days-of-image-processing&quot;&gt;101 Days Of Image Processing&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company I work with have its core-technology dealing with image processing. But because of my bad aptitude for math, as well as being holed inside my own work. The knowledge I have in this domain is very little.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to attempt at understanding practical side of image processing as well as its underlying principles. For that I been reading &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Digital-Image-Processing-Rafael-Gonzalez/dp/0133356728/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1508741069&amp;amp;sr=8-1&amp;amp;keywords=digital+image+processing&quot;&gt;Digital Image Processing&lt;/a&gt;. Though the first two chapters gave me insights about basics. Getting into Digital Signal Processing part my ability to follow up with the book went off the rails. Instead of hitting my head hard to understand the text, I decided to use it as a reference and explore the field quite a bit on my own. With basic principles, I inted to dive to the implmentation side of the subject. As a goal marker I dedicating 101 days toward this while journaling the whole thing as a way of better understanding and to serve as a medium of reference to any others who are in a position similar to mine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I won’t be able to put continious 101 days toward it, though atleast I will try to put in 2 days every week towards this. Wish me luck!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">101 Days Of Image Processing</summary></entry></feed>